Guide to the Graphic Communications International Union, Local 767M Records 1908-2009
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Graphic Communications International Union, Local 767M records
1894-2011
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5644
Graphic Communications International Union.$bLocal 767M (Seattle, Wash.)
91.23 cubic feet 86 boxes
Records of the Union
Labor organization of the printing industry began as early as 1836, with the first meeting of the National Typographical Society, later renamed the International Typographical Union (ITU) in Washington, D.C. However, it wasn’t until the late 1800s that mechanization transformed the printing industry into a full-scale trade with craft specialization. Newspaper printing and commercial printing became distinct trades. By the turn of the century several separate printing unions had emerged or seceded from the ITU, including the International Printing Pressmen Union of North America (IPPU) in 1897 and the Amalgamated Lithographers of America (ALA) in 1915. Union membership flourished in the first half of the 20th century, and the unions were able to operate alone. As union membership declined in the later half of century, a series of mergers occurred. The International Printing and Graphic Communications Union (IPGCU) resulted in 1973 from the merger of the IPPU and the International Stereotypers’ and Electroplaters’ Union (IS&EU). In 1983, the IPGCU merged with the Graphic Arts International Union (GAIU) to form the Graphic Communications International Union (GCIU). In 2005, the GCIU decided to merge with the 1.1 million member Teamster union.
The first printing union in Seattle was the International Brotherhood of Bookbinders (IBB) in 1900. Seven years later, the Seattle Web Printing Pressmen & Assistants’s Union No. 26 was formed. In 1963, Local No. 26 merged with five other Washington printers’ unions to create the Washington state Joint Crafts Council. GCIU branch 767-M was the result of the 1985 merger of PH & PPU Local 50, GCIU Local 26N and GCIU Local 530M. In 1996, GCIU Local 292-M of Portland, Oregon merged with GCIU 767-M. Additionally, between 2002 and 2003, GCIU branches in Bremerton (367-M), Olympia (182-C) and Aberdeen (262-C) merged with Local 767-M, further strengthening the Seattle branch. In 2005, 767-M merged with the Teamster Union. 767-M still exists today.
This collection documents the various activities of several branches of the Graphic Communications Conference of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters located in the Pacific Northwest of the United States. The collection spans from 1908-2011, with the bulk of the materials dated post-1970. This collection contains papers that originated in the Seattle branch 767-M of the GCIU, as well as documents that were collected at the time of its creation as well as through subsequent mergers. The documents are from several branches within the state of Washington (Seattle, Aberdeen, Tacoma and Olympia), as well as Portland, Oregon. The oldest files are from Seattle Web Pressmen’s Union No. 26. The collection details the activities of the Union and its members, as well as the relations between the Union and employers. The largest part of the collection documents Contracts and Contract Negotiations (Series III), shining a light on the issues that were most pertinent to both the Union and employers, as well as the changes over time in the way contracts were negotiated. While many of the documents related to medical and financial benefits can be found in these contract files, the remainder are detailed in Benefits (series VII). Of particular note are the Legal Files (Series V), which offer insight into the various arbitration and grievance cases brought up by the Union and the resulting settlements. Further details into the communication between employers and the Union, as well as contact between multiple branches of the Union, can be drawn from Correspondence (Series II). The day to day workings of several earlier branches of the Union can be assessed from the Executive Board and General Union Minutes/By-Laws (Series I), Office Files (Series VI) and Financial Records (Series VII). In addition, Merger Files (Series IV) highlight the policies related to various Union mergers that led up to the 2004 iteration of the GCIU.
Access is restricted. Contact the Special Collections division of the University of Washington Libraries for details.
Graphic Communications International Union.$bLocal 767M (Seattle, Wash.)$vArchives; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington)
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Journalism; Labor Unions; Labor History; Publishers and Publishing; Washington (State); Seattle
- Graphic Communications International Union, Local 767M Records, 1908-2009; 5644-001; 15.38 cubic feet 16 boxes
  Access is restricted. Contact the Special Collections division of the University of Washington Libraries for details.
  Donor: Brian Earl, president, August 9, 2011.
  This collection is arranged into 8 series:
  Series I: Executive Board and General Union Minutes/By-Laws, 1908-2001
  Series II: Correspondence, 1924-2002
  Series III: Contracts/Contract Negotiations, 1911-2011
  Series IV: Merger Files, 1942, 1963-2004
  Series V: Legal Files, 1911-1953
  Series VI: Office Files, 1908-2001
  Series VII: Financial Records, 1916-1985
  Series VIII: Benefits, 1990-2003
  The series are arranged by document format or function and then further arranged by their creator. Within these sub-series, files are arranged chronologically by date of the oldest document in the file. Due to the file management of the Union, there is some overlap between series. For example, many of the files from Contracts/Contract Negotiation (Series III) contain correspondence unrelated to contract negotiations, which would otherwise belong in Correspondence (Series II).
  Photographic prints, film reels, and videocassette tapes were extracted from this accession and placed in the Graphic Communications International Union, Local 767M Visual Materials Collection (PH 1150). This collection contains approximately 30 photographic prints, 3 film reels and 37 video cassette tapes.
  The visual materials that form part of this collection are described and indexed in
  A Guide to the Graphic Communications International Union, Local 767M Photographs and Moving Images
  .
  - EXECUTIVE BOARD AND GENERAL UNION MINUTES/BY-LAWS, 1908-2001; SERIES I
    Series I includes extensive minutes of Seattle Web Pressmen’s Union No. 26, as well as the minutes of a handful of local union branches. This series also includes the By-Laws of a few local unions dated 1970-1993.
    The series is subdivided by function, and further arranged within each sub-series numerically according to the local union number of the originating body: Sub-series A: Minutes, 1908-2001; Part 1: Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1923-1989; Part 2: General Union Meeting Minutes, 1908-2001; Sub-series B: By-Laws, 1970-1993.
    - Minutes, 1908-2001; Subseries A
      - Part 1: Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1923-1989
        - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1923-1984 (Box-folder 1/1-9)
          - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1923-1932 (Box-folder 1/1)
          - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1951 (Box-folder 1/2)
          - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1952-1959 (Box-folder 1/3)
          - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 1/4)
          - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 1/5)
          - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 1/6)
          - Executive Board Reports, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 1/7)
          - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 1/8)
          - Executive Board Reports, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 1/9)
        - Executive Board Minutes Local 262-C, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 6/46)
        - Local 292 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Part 2: General Union Minutes, 1908-2001
        - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1908-1979
          - General Union & Special Minutes, 1908-1913 (Box-folder 3/1)
          - General Union Meeting Minutes, 1914-1923 (Box-folder 1/10)
          - General Union Meeting Minutes, 1932-1945 (Box-folder 1/11)
          - General Union Meeting Minutes Local No. 26, 1945-1952 (Box-folder 2/1)
          - General Union Meeting Minutes Local No. 26, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 2/2)
          - General Union Meeting Minutes Local No. 26, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 2/3)
          - General Union Meeting Minutes Local No. 26, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 2/4)
          - General Union Meeting Minutes Local No. 26, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 2/5)
        - Local 182-C Meeting Minutes Book, 1984-2001 (Box-folder 13/21)
        - Local 292 Regular Meeting Minutes, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - By-laws, 1970-1993; Subseries B
      - Local 202 By-laws, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - By-Laws Local 292M and Local 87, 1971; 1983 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Tacoma Local 49 By-Laws, 1974-1993 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1924-2002; SERIES II
    Series II includes correspondence between various unions and employers, as well as correspondence between different local unions.
    The series is subdivided by originating body and arranged chronologically: Subseries A: Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1924-1952; Subseries B: Local 219 Correspondence, 1961-1963; Subseries C: Correspondence with Eugene Macellari, 1963-1969; Subseries D: Local 87-B Correspondence, 1966-1973; Subseries E: Local 23-P Correspondence, 1971-1976; Subseries F: Local 262 Correspondence, 1980-2993; Subseries G: Local 767-M Correspondence, 1988-2002; Subseries H: City of Seattle Correspondence, 1990-2000; Subseries I: Local 182-C Correspondence, 1990-2004. Within each sub-series, files are arranged chronologically.
    - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1924-1952; Subseries A
      - Seattle Times Correspondence, 1924-1959 (Box-folder 12/25-26)
      - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26 Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1932-1952 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Local 219 Correspondence, 1961-1963; Subseries B (Box-folder 13/27)
    - Correspondence with Eugene Macellari, 1963-1968; Subseries C (Box-folder 13/30-31)
    - Local 87-B Correspondence, 1966-1973; Subseries D
      - Safeco Insurance Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Local 23-P Correspondence, 1971-1976; Subseries E (Box-folder 12/24)
    - Local 262 Correspondence, 1980-1993; Subseries F
      - Graphic Communications International Union Local 262-C Misc. Correspondence, 1980-1993 (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Washingtonian Print Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1993 (Box-folder 6/33)
    - Local 767-M Correspondence, 1988-2002; Subseries G
      - American Envelope Company (and Successors) Correspondence, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 11/27)
      - Local 767-M Correspondence/Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Local 767-M Portland Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - Print Northwest Correspondence, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Quebecor Integrated Media Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Ross Printing Correspondence, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - United Graphics Correspondence, 1988-1998 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - City of Seattle Correspondence, 1990-2000; Subseries H
      - City of Seattle Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 10/30)
      - City of Seattle Correspondence, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 10/31)
      - City of Seattle Correspondence, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Local 182-C Correspondence, 1990-2004; Subseries I (Box-folder 13/19-20)
    - Local 367-C Correspondence, 1998-2001; Subseries J (Box-folder 13/15)
  - CONTRACTS/CONTRACT NEGOTIATIONS, 1911-2011; SERIES III
    Series III includes contracts between various unions and employers, as well as memorandum, minutes, correspondence and voting records that relate to contract negotiations. The bulk of these files originated from Local 767-M, although many contracts relate to other local unions. Also included are disclaimers of interest, which give insight into why employers and unions decided to end contracts.
    The series is subdivided by function: Subseries A: Contracts/Contract Negotiations, 1911-2011; Subseries B: Disclaimers of Interest-Local 767-M. Subseries A is further divided by creator and arranged chronologically: Part 1: Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1911-1985; Part 2: Aberdeen-Hoquiam Pressmens Union No. 262, 1951-1993; Part 3: Local 767-M Contracts, 1972-2011; Part 4: Local 87-B, 1975; Part 5: Local 202, 1975-1985; Part 6: Local 530, 1971-1991; Part 7: Joint Crafts Council, 1981-2006; Part 8: Local 292-M, 1986-1992; Part 9: Local 149-B, 1987-1994. Within each of these sub-series, files are arranged alphabetically according to employer name. Part 10: Blank Printing Contracts is located at the end of the series.
    - Contracts/Contract Negotiations, 1911-2011; Subseries A
      - Part 1: Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1911-1985
        - Joint Operating Arrangement Between Seattle Newspaper Web Pressmen's Union #26 and The Seattle Times, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 12/28)
        - The Seattle Times and Seattle Paper Handlers Contracts, 1931-1959 (Box-folder 13/24)
        - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26 Contracts, 1911-1938 (Box-folder 2/12)
        - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26 Contracts, 1940-1957 (Box-folder 2/11)
        - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26 Contracts, 1957-1968 (Box-folder 2/10)
        - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26 Contracts, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 2/9)
        - Skagit Valley Herald Contract Negotiations, 1971-1985 (Box-folder 4/43)
        - Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26 - Correspondence and Contracts, 1919-1975 (Box-folder 13/26)
      - Part 2: Aberdeen-Hoquiam Pressmens Union No. 262, 1951-1993
        - Aberdeen Daily World f/k/a Grays Harbor Publishing Company, 1951-1971
          - Grays Harbor Publishing Company Contract, 1951-1955 (Box-folder 6/43)
          - Aberdeen Daily World (f/k/a Grays Harbor Publishing Company) Commercial Printing Contract, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 6/26)
          - Aberdeen Daily World (f/k/a Grays Harbor Publishing Company) Commercial Printing Contract, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/27)
        - Bellingham Herald Negotiations, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 12/23)
        - Bremerton Sun Contract Negotiations, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 12/22)
        - The Buyers Guide, Inc./Metropolitan Press Printing Co./News Publishing Co. Contracts, 1929-1969 (Box-folder 12/21)
        - Grays Harbor Stamp Works Commercial Printing Contract, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 6/27)
        - Grays Harbor Washingtonian d/b/a Washingtonian Print, 1951-1993
          - Grays Harbor Washingtonian Commercial Print Contract, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 6/34)
          - Grays Harbor Washingtonian Commercial Print Contract, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 6/35)
          - Washingtonian Print (f/k/a Grays Harbor Washingtonian) Commercial Printing Contract, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 6/36)
          - Washingtonian Print (f/k/a Grays Harbor Washingtonian) Contract, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 6/37)
          - Washingtonian Print (f/k/a Grays Harbor Washingtonian) Contract, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 6/38)
          - Washingtonian Print (f/k/a Grays Harbor Washingtonian) Contract, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 6/39)
          - Washingtonian Print (f/k/a Grays Harbor Washingtonian) Contract, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 6/40)
          - Washingtonian Print (f/k/a Grays Harbor Washingtonian) Contract, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 6/41)
          - Washingtonian Print (f/k/a Grays Harbor Washingtonian) Contract, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 6/42)
        - Moe Printing Company, 1951-1965
          - Moe Printing Company Commercial Printing Contract, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 6/29)
          - Moe Printing Company Commercial Printing Contract, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 6/30)
        - Quick Print Company, 1951-1963
          - Quick Print Company Commercial Printing Contract, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 6/31)
          - Quick Print Company Commercial Printing Contract, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 6/32)
      - Part 3: Local 767-M Contracts, 1972-2011
        - 2nd Phrase Printing, 1992-2002
          - 2nd Phrase Printing Contract Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 7/11)
          - 2nd Phrase Printing Contract Negotiations, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 7/10)
          - 2nd Phrase Printing Contract Negotiations, 1986; 1996-1999 (Box-folder 7/9)
          - 2nd Phrase Printing Contract Negotiations, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 7/8)
        - 4C Graphics, 2002-2005
          - 4C Graphics Contract Negotiations, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 7/13)
          - 4C Graphics Contract Negotiations, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 7/12)
        - A&B Printing, 1990-2011
          - A&B Printing Contract Negotiations, 2008-2011 (Box-folder 7/7)
          - A&B Printing Contract Negotiations, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 7/6)
          - A&B Printing Contract Negotiations, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 7/5)
          - A&B Printing Contract Negotiations, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 7/4)
          - A&B Printing Contract Negotiations, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 7/3)
          - A&B Printing Contract Negotiations, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 7/2)
          - A&B Printing Contract Negotiations, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 7/1)
        - A&H Printers Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 7/54)
        - A&L Printing F/K/A K&P Printing, 1997-2010
          - K&P Printing Contract Negotiations, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 8/12)
          - K&P Printing Contract Negotiations/Disclaimer of Interest, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 8/13)
          - K&P Printing Contract Negotiations, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 8/11)
          - K&P Printing Contract Negotiations, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8/10)
          - K&P Printing Contract Negotiations, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 8/9)
          - K&P Printing Contract Negotiations, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 8/8)
          - K&P Printing Contract Negotiations, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 8/7)
          - A&L Printing F/K/A K&P Printing Contract Negotiations, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 8/6)
          - A&L Printing F/K/A K&P Printing Contract Negotiations, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 8/5)
        - Accents Printing & Copying Inc. Contract, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 6/3)
        - Air Power Graphics, 1989-1999
          - Air Power Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 9/20)
          - Air Power Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 9/19)
          - Air Power Graphics Contract, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 9/18)
          - Air Power Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 9/17)
        - All Color Printing, 1995-2008
          - All Color Printing Contract Negotiations, 1986; 1995-1997 (Box-folder 13/6)
          - All Color Printing Contract Negotiations, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 13/5)
          - All Color Printing Contract Negotiations, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 13/4)
          - All Color Printing Contract Negotiations, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 13/3)
          - All Color Printing Contract Negotiations, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 13/2)
        - Aloha Printing Contract, 2002 (Box-folder 7/14)
        - American Envelope Company, 1985-2002
          - Northwest Envelope Company (d/b/a American Envelope Company) Contract Negotiations and Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 11/8)
          - American Envelope Company (and Successors) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1995 (Box-folder 11/18-19)
          - American Envelope Contract, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 11/9)
          - American Envelope Company (and Successors) Contract Negotiations with Various Local Unions, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 11/10-11)
          - American Mail-Well Envelope Contract Negotiations, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 11/21-22)
          - Mail-Well Envelope Contract Negotiations, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 11/23-25)
        - Bayless Bindery, 1985-1995
          - Bayless Bindery Contracts, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 9/34)
          - Bayless Bindery 1991 Contract Negotiations, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 9/32-33)
          - Bayless Bindery 1994 Wage Opener, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 9/31)
        - Beaverdam Press d/b/a Homestead Cards, 1996-2004
          - Beaverdam Press Contract Negotiations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 12/3)
          - Homestead Cards/Beaverdam Press Contract Negotiations, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 12/2)
          - Homestead Cards Contract Negotiations, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 12/1)
        - Biallas Printing Contract Negotiations, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 9/22)
        - Button Place Contract Negotiations, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 6/1)
        - Chesapeake Press, 1985-2005
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Negotiations, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 4/15)
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Negotiations, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 4/16)
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Negotiations, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 4/17)
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Extension, 1991 (Box-folder 4/18)
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 4/19)
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Negotiations, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 4/20)
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 4/21)
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Negotiations, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 4/22)
          - Chesapeake Press Contract Negotiations, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 4/23)
        - Clinton Hull Printing Contract Negotiations, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 5/34)
        - Columbia Basin Printers & Print Graphics, Inc., 1978-1984 (Box-folder 8/25)
        - Country Lane, Inc., 1995-2004
          - Country Lane, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 5/23)
          - Country Lane, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 5/24)
          - Country Lane, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 5/25)
        - The Craftsman Press, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 6/4)
        - Creative Color Services Corporation, 1986-2003
          - Creative Color Service Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 9/39)
          - Creative Color Service Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 9/38)
          - Creative Color Service Corporation Contract Negotiations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 9/37)
        - Del Information Services, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 7/17)
        - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co., 1992-2005
          - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 4/9)
          - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 4/10)
          - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 4/11)
          - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1999-2005 (Box-folder 4/12)
        - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service, 1986-2011
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 10/13)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 10/12)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 10/11)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 10/10)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 10/9)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 10/8)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 10/7)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 10/6)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 2002-2009 (Box-folder 10/5)
          - Diamond Press & Direct Mail Service Contract Negotiations, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 10/4)
        - Direct Mail Network Contract Negotiations, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 13/1)
        - Discount Printing Contract Negotiations, 1990-1994; 1986 (Box-folder 13/7)